shoptoit.ca 2018-01-13

# Privacy Policy - Fashion Trends, Articles, and Sale Prices Online in Canada at Shoptoit

The Shop To It Inc. application and the associated Shop To It Inc. website available at www.shoptoit.ca (collectively, "Shop To It Inc.") are owned and operated by Shop To It Inc. ("us" "we" or "our"). This Shop To It Inc. privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any information you submit to us through Shop To It Inc. This includes "Personal Information," which is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, e-mail address, user ID number, and other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing, as well as "Anonymous Information," which is information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information and does not permit the identification of individual persons. 

### User Consent

By accessing or otherwise using Shop To It Inc., you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information and Anonymous Information according to this Privacy Policy. 

Your Personal Information may be processed by us in the country where it was collected as well as other countries where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. 

### Concerning Children

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use Shop To It in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or guardian. 

We will never knowingly collect the personal information of minors. 

### Collection and Use of Information

In general our collection of personal information is described below in the following key sources of collection and site activities: 

  * Information Voluntarily Submitted: Information voluntarily submitted for creating or editing your account and user profile on Shop To It Inc.. When you personalize your profile and use the features of Shop To It Inc., we collect any information you voluntarily provide, and we may also request optional information to support your use of Shop To It Inc., such as your year of birth, gender and other demographic information.

  * Content Submissions: Information voluntarily submitted during your use of the Shop To It Inc. site which can include content as photos, reviews, ratings and other information you choose to submit.

  * Personal Information from Other Sources: Personal information from other sources with which you have registered, companies with whom we have partnered with (collectively, "Partners") or other third parties. For example, we may collect your user ID or profile information that you have permitted to be displayed through Shop To It Inc. in order to display you as a friend or in association with your profile and collections. We may associate this information with the other Personal Information we have collected about you. We may also collect information about you and your friends who use Shop To It Inc., from any social network you may have connected from, in order to provide you with a more personalized experience.

  * Payments: When you purchase the items offered on Shop To It Inc., you will need to submit your credit card or other payment information so that our service providers can process your payment for those products and services. When you sign up for, or win, any special auctions, sweepstakes, or other activities that we make available on Shop To It Inc., we will collect or utilize the information designated along with such activity, which may include your contact information such as your address and phone number.

  * Email Addresses: If you send an e-mail to us, or fill out our "Feedback" form through Shop To It Inc., we may file electronically your e-mail address and the full content of your e-mail, including attached files, and other information you provide. We may use and display your full name and email address when you send an email notification to a friend through Shop To It Inc. or the social network from which you have connected to Shop To It Inc. (such as in an invitation, or when sharing your content). We will use your e-mail address to contact you, for things such as notifications of our daily offers and other special offers or contests and other related information. You may indicate your preference to stop receiving further promotional communications as further detailed below.

  * Use of Technology: Information collected through the use of technology such as your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system collected to make Shop To It Inc. and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the experience with Shop To It Inc. to meet your special interests and needs. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on Shop To It Inc. you clicked. In order to use our services offered through Shop To It Inc., your web browser must accept Cookies.

  * Third-Party Advertising: We may also enable advertisers and ad servers to promote third-party products and/or services by placing advertisements on Shop To It Inc.. These advertisers and ad servers may use Cookies and/or "Web Beacons" (which are usually small, transparent graphic images) in order to monitor information related to served advertisements. Clicking on such advertisements will direct you to the website of a third-party and the advertiser. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy practices of any advertisers or ad servers.

### Use and Disclosure of Information

Shop To It Inc. generally does not sell, trade, rent, or share the Personal Information that we collect with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so or otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want us to use or disclose Personal Information collected about you in the manners identified in this Privacy Policy, you may not use Shop To It Inc..

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that would otherwise make the Anonymous Information personally identifiable to you. Generally, we aggregate this information and use it in statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of Shop To It Inc.. This Privacy Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of any Anonymous Information in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties in our discretion.

Consistent with our intent to protect your privacy, the personal information you submit to us is used to provide you access to Shop To It Inc., to improve Shop To It Inc., customize your experience, and to offer you additional information, opportunities, promotions and functionality from us, our partners or our advertisers at your request. We do share your content preferences and other information with the social network from which you have connected to Shop To It Inc., along with those companies and persons you have asked us to share your information with.

We may provide your Personal Information to third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of Shop To It Inc. and to help us communicate with you. These services may include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service. We require our third-party service providers to promise not to use such information except as necessary to provide the relevant services to us. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our third-party partners, those with whom we have a co-branding or promotional relationship, or other third-parties about whom you are otherwise notified and do not request to opt out of such sharing.

Shop To It Inc. is a private company. In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. As part of the business transition we may share some or all of your Personal Information with these companies, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy.

You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer's assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property, you, or third parties. You hereby consent to us sharing your Personal Information under the circumstances described herein. 

### Information for Public View

Shop To It Inc. may provide content areas on our Website where you can publicly post information, communicate with others, or review products and vendors. This information may be accessible by other Shop To It Inc. users and site visitors and companies. Publicly posted content may appear on other websites or web searches, and your public information could be read, collected, and used by others. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information.

### Third Party Sites and Advertising

Shop To It Inc. may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through Shop To It Inc. and does not apply to these third-party websites. The ability to access information of third-parties from Shop To It Inc., or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their products, their services, other websites, locations or their content.

### Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly at [info@shoptoit.ca](mailto:info@shoptoit.ca) or by mailing Shop To It Inc. Suite L100, 239-10th Ave SE Calgary AB Canada T2G 0V9.

Despite your indicated email preferences, we may send you administrative emails regarding Shop To It Inc., including, for example, administrative confirmations, and notices of updates to our Privacy Policy if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner. 

### Updating or Removing Your Information

You may choose to correct, update, or delete the membership information you have submitted to us by sending an email requesting changes to info@shoptoit.ca. Furthermore, if we inadvertently collect more personal information than intended, we endeavor to delete the extraneous information.

Please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request, only after we have fulfilled such requirements). However, please understand that deleted information may continue to persist on backup media. 

### Feedback

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You agree that any such comments and any email we receive becomes our property. We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our services without paying any royalties or other compensation to you. 

### Security

We are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. Information submitted through the shopping and registration processes are encrypted through a Secured Socket Layer (SSL) connection, which protects the information in transit.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information. 

### Contact and Revisions

Shop To It Inc.'s Privacy Policy may change from time to time. However, any revised privacy policy will be consistent with our services. If we make any substantive changes to our policies, we will post notice of changes on this page and by email to all current registered users of Shop To It Inc..  
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or anything else, please contact us at: [info@shoptoit.ca](mailto:info@shoptoit.ca)
